finally
a quality signature sense that is a very
affordable price
the new inspired by bulgarian amethyst
from
viper theme collection a perfume that is
very moisturizing on the skin and can
last for long
hours inspired by bulgarian amethyst for
only 225 passes
just used to code viper shinto promerans
from july 8 up until august 31 2020.
[Music]
hey there guys it's me chantal and for
today's video guys i will be sharing
with you this local brand of perfume na
very long-lasting onsen and very
affordable and private and hiriku
guys if you're a friend of mine probably
naked
story specialist story and some
messenger story diva
and guys in bran
perfume collection or vive.com if ever
in a game interested give us a product
and i will put their social media
accounts here and also the description
box yes
in the first part that's right guys
marion putai
on discount code and sale and by perfume
so if you want to avail that 10 discount
on your product chosen product then
use my code viper chantal
so from 250 pesos i'm getting 225 pesos
hello
especially small students like us and
guys you know me i'm a perfume collector
so if you haven't watched my perfume
collection then i will link it down in
the description box
all right guys so mama
light blue versace bride crystal
bulgari omnia amethyst encantoshine
elizabeth arden green tea joe malone
nectarian honey and blossoms cucumber
melon
v and s are victoria's secret vanilla
romantic wish and lacoste pink
and guys in vilang vesta for women and
sentinel via perfume quesadilla for men
and
cool water dng light blue hugo boss
classic
la coste white bulgari aquamarine
paco rabban one million apollo sport
and tommy boy
okay guys to give you a little
background the vibe perfume collection
i will give you their mission and vision
which is to provide quality perfumes
with the budget friendly product
that can be enjoyed by everyone
and your vision of appointment by
perfume is to create
a quality signature sense and make
people's day today with just
one spray in the core personally guys
you need
a more completely go without spraying a
perfume kite
very positive and vibrant
again i know guys
inspired by bulgari omnia amethyst
so this is one of the best sellers now
women sent down vip perfume collection
so at the
end bottle
so basically
so it is a powdery floral scent that
brings to mind the violet colored
gemstone
the scent begins with the distinct top
note of
pink grapefruit fresh juicy and bright
so guys let's try again
var perfume collection
friends as in no joke i'm telling you
this
honestly and this is my honest review
about the viper film collection so you
guys spin up
on the owner if powdery
fruity like that and you know me guys
alcoholic banana
perfume and
[Music]
perfume and i super duper love it
like sobrang amazed a quality nova
perfume affordable price and yet baby
game catalog
quality signature sense
my second comment guys is that hindi
now yeah compared to others so this one
guys but i'm formulated
[Music]
my final comment guys and you mostly
natawa ako
is that very affordable and priced now
imagine for 250 pesos guys
american among high and this instant
perfume like manga yo
250 pesos long guys and 95
ml bottle like this
if you're looking for a budget friendly
very affordable
moisturizing skin formulated price
sensitive skin oil based and perfume
friendly then kindly
check out this vive perfume collection
so that's it guys for today's video and
if ever in a game interested pukayosa
vibe perfume collection
and congo sonya pong ma try young sen na
binigamosa agena owner then
check out their social media accounts
their facebook
and ig account in the link within the
description box below
and guys
and don't forget to use my code guys
vibration
i'm 10 discount and guys this promo will
only run
until august 31 2020 so in the pilot
guys my chance for pohayon huma ball
now manga perfumes nagos so guys before
these videos i just wanted to thank vibe
perfume collection
and also to ativan now for trusting me
to be one of their brand ambassadors
so guys if you have any video
suggestions then please do comment down
below
follow me on all of my social media
accounts and if you like this video then
please do give me a big thumbs up
and don't forget to subscribe to my
channel again it's chantalati
bye guys see you again on my next vlog
[Music]
you